(Raj:)These spring rolls are amazing.
Good job, Bernadette.
(Bernadette:)That's the takeout that Sheldon brought.
(Raj:)I'm sure they wouldn't have tasted nearly as
good if I hadn't tried your food first.
(Sheldon:)Howard, did you want your clothes
arranged seasonally or by color?
- Color's fine.
- Wrong, they'll be arranged seasonally.
(Penny:)Aren't you gonna spend
a little time with Amy?
(Amy:)Oh, it's okay, I'm used to it.
(Amy:)The other day at Whole Foods, he spent
an hour optimizing the cheese aisle.
(Sheldon:)And some thanks I got.
(Sheldon:)The assistant manager chased me out
with an artisanal salami.
(Amy:)His quirks just make you love him more.
(Amy:)Someone please agree with me.
(Leonard:)Come on. It's getting late. Time to go.